这是你的辩诉交易条款，Mr. Fallin
Here are the terms of your plea bargain, Mr. Fallin.
3年缓刑期
3 years probation,
10000美元罚金
$10,000 fine,
而且你看起来似乎……
And since you seem so...
很精通于企业法
Clearly adept at working in corporate law,
那么我现在要判决你
I am sentencing you
为儿童法律服务部（CLS）
To 1,500 hours of community service,
进行1500小时的义务劳动
Working for children's Legal services
你在那里的工作是儿童律师
As a child advocate.
快点儿，快，我们走
Come on, hurry up. Let's go.
等等我
Wait a minute.
快点，我们走，伙计们
Hurry up. Let's go, guys.
儿童法律服务部的工作任务很简单
The mission of children's Legal services is simple.
我们为那些被虐待、被忽视
We provide quality Legal representation
以及其他处于危险中的孩子们
And advocacy assistance to children who are abused,
提供高质量的法律援助
Neglected, or otherwise at risk.
我们希望保护这些孩子免受更多的伤害
We hope to protect these kids from future harm.
我相信你已经习惯了更优越的环境
I'm sure you're used to Better surroundings,
但是这里可是非盈利机构
But here in The not-for-profit world,
我们没得可选择，不能苛求
We tend to beg instead of choose.
我们这里的9个全职律师，一年要处理4000多个案子
Our 9 full-time attorneys handle over 4,000 cases a year.
他们努力一年的薪水是27000美元，外加奖金福利
For their efforts they receive $27,000 annually, plus benefits.
我知道我们的酬劳无法和公司白领比
I know our remuneration doesn't compare to corporate life,
不过我们的目的不是金钱，Mr.Fallin
But our cases aren't About money, Mr. Fallin.
而是为了让孩子们的生活有所改变
They're about making the difference in a child's life.
早上好，Barbara
Good morning, Barbara.
早安
Good morning.
我在县政府博物馆工作的时候，和你的父亲搭伙
I served on the county museum board With your father.
他，他也许还记得我
He, uh, He may remember me.
我当时参与筹备了
I was integral in planning
在Oliver Heights举办的
A charity golf for cancer weekend
一场为癌症患者捐款的周末慈善高尔夫球会
At Oliver Heights Country club.
我爹不打高尔夫
My dad doesn't golf.
是吧，好，这个，我刚才说了
Yes, well, uh, As I was saying,
我们儿童法律服务部的哲学
our philosophy here At the children's Legal services
是非常简单的
Is quite simple.
我们……我们代表了孩子们的心声
We... we represent the child's wishes.
那就是我们的工作，那就是我们坚守在这儿的原因
That's our job, That's why we're here.
我们认为孩子们有权利要求人们的倾听与理解
We feel that children have a right to be heard and respected.
你同意吗，Mr. Fallin
Don't you agree, Mr. Fallin?
很好
Very well, then.
明天早上，在法院那里
James Mooney will be giving you your hands-on orientation
James Mooney会把具体的工作情况告诉你的
Tomorrow morning at the courthouse.
你还有什么要问我的吗
Do you have any questions for me?
是的，这次，花了39分钟
Yeah. This, Uh, took 39 minutes.
你可以给我记成1个小时吗
Can you mark me for an hour?
大家都进教室了
Let's get in there.
快点，进来了
Come on, let's go.
快点，孩子们，快，快
Let's go, guys. Come on, hurry, hurry.
这是最后一遍铃了，快点
That was the late bell. Let's get going. Come on.
快点，快，快点，Hunter
Come on. Come on. Come on, Hunter!
Hunter?
出什么事了
What happened?
Hunter? Hunter.
快来人呐，我需要帮助
I need some help here. Somebody!
Fallin法律服务部
法外情真
第一季 第一集
主演 Simon Baker
你得了解法律法规、法庭程序
Gotta go over the legal standards, Court process,
儿童成长知识，与孩子们沟通的技巧
Child development, Interviewing tactics for children,
性虐待方面的
Investigating Protocols,
生理和心理上的医疗证据
Nature of physical and medical evidence
以及相关的调查协议，文化……
of sexual abuse, Cultural...
我20分钟后还有个会议
I have a meeting in 20 minutes.
今天我们要进行的是监护听证
Today we're doing Shelter hearings.
你知道是怎么回事吗
You know what those are?
那个是法庭判决是否有必要
That's when a court decides if there's a clear necessity
剥夺父母对孩子的监护权
to remove a child from his or her home.
看来你知道该怎么做了
So, you know what to do?
我先去见见孩子，问问他们的诉求
I see the child, I ask them what they want,
然后，我把这些诉求上报法官，还有别的什么吗
I tell it to the judge. What else is there?
你知道吗，我从来也没想要在公司里工作
You know, I never wanted to be a corporate guy.
当然，我也没那个本事
Wouldn't have been able to, anyway.
如果你只有夜校文凭
See, hard to go Corporate
那就很难挤进公司工作
When your degree Reads night school.
如果人们看你的肤色来决定的话，就难上加难
Harder still When your skin reads the projects,
你明白我在说什么吗
You know what I'm saying?
你想表达什么
What's your point?
这种工作……
This kind of job...
并不适合每个人
Is not for everyone.
这个工作需要有热情的
Takes a person who's passionate
能关心他人的，有所担当的人来做
and caring and committed.
这里没有第二次机会
There are no second chances here.
倘若你搞砸了一个受虐儿童的案子的话
You screw up with a kid who's been abused
你便没有机会再弥补过错
And you don't get that chance back.
你不来吗
You coming?
我先去解个手，马上就去
I just gotta take a leak. I'll catch up.
在C-7房
Room c-7.
知道了
Got it.
你就是CLS新来的人吗
You're the new guy from CLS?
我想是的，不过我要去开会，我都已经迟到了
I guess I am, But I'm late for a meeting.
这是你的委托人，Hunter Reed
Meet Hunter Reed, Your newest client.
Nicholas Fallin，我赶着要去开会
Nicholas Fallin. I'm late for a meeting.
你的案子在15分钟后开始审理
You're on the dock Et in 15 minutes.
过来
Come here.
说你呢，过来
Seriously, come here.
法庭程序是怎样的
What's court process?
你不知道吗
You don't know.
我从没有正式上过法庭
I've never officially been in court.
Hunter...
来，坐这儿，好吗，亲爱的
Here, sit over here, Would you, sweetie?
你瞅啥呢
What are you looking at?
西装不错
Nice suit.
你叫什么
What's your name?
Laurie Solt.
Laurie Solt，这儿不属于我
Laurie Solt, this is not my world,
我不可能因为我这身制服而道歉
And I am not about to apologize for wearing my uniform.
你的制服
Your uniform?
听着，你有你的角色，对吧
Listen, you play Your role, right?
你是个社会公益工作者，你甘愿受穷
You're a social worker who chooses to make no money.
不过，相反的是你还向这个世界哭穷
Instead, you cry poor to the world.
你穿着廉价的衣服，所以人们知道
You wear cheap clothes so people know
你是打哪里来的
where you're coming from.
我的世界是富贵的
My world is expensive.
我并不是说我比你强
I'm not saying it's any better.
只是这两种世界有不同的法则，你得接受
It just has different rules. So be it.
你有什么问题
What is your problem?
我的问题是我没说，嘿，你看起来像是垃圾
My problem is I didn't say, hey, You look like crap,
所以如果你能克制你自己不再讽刺我穿得体面的话
So I would appreciate it If you would refrain
我会十分感谢的
from beating me up for looking decent.
现在，我们可以回到我最初的问题了吗
Now, could we please return to my initial question?
法庭程序……
Court procedure...
提交案件，传唤证人
Cases called, Witnesses are called.
社会公益代理律师提交案件
Social service agency attorney puts on her case,
父母方律师陈述他们的主张
Parents' attorney put on theirs,
陈述后，就轮到你了
The trumpets sound, and it's your turn.
我该做些什么
What do I do?
你要总结陈述你的态度
You summarize your position
提出你的处理意见，明白了吗
And state your recommendations. Got it?
开庭时见吧
See you in court.
会议室就在那边
The conference room is right over there.
也许你应该先跟你的当事人了解一下情况
Maybe you should interview your client.
这上面说你的父亲在监狱里
It says your father's in jail
在城里你还有姥姥，姥爷，他们此时正在度假中
And you have grandparents in the city who are on vacation.
那么，你爸爸因为什么进了监狱
Now, why is your dad in jail?
你妈妈呢
Where's your mom?
你想和你的姥姥，姥爷住在一起吗
You want to live with your grandparents?
好吧，我们不说这个了……
Ok, let's just cut to it...
Hunter.
我是你的律师，你马上要参加一个监护听证会
I'm your lawyer. You're about to enter a shelter hearing
在会上，法官会作出决定
In which it will be decided
你是否还会继续和你的父母在一起
Whether or not you will be removed from your home.
你对此有什么想法吗
Do you have any thoughts on that?
听着，孩子，我没有时间
Listen, kid, I don't have the time
坐在这里等你回答
to sit here and beg you for answers.
根据这张表格判断，你的姥姥，姥爷家
Judging from the form, your grandparents
是最符合逻辑的，适合你去住的地方
is the logical place for you to be,
所以我们就告诉法庭，让你去那吧
So let's just tell the court to place you there
就这么定了
And get this over with.
第2457号案件，Hunter Reed
Case number 2457. Hunter reed.
案子什么情况
Why are we here?
这是Hunter Reed，法官大人
This is Hunter Reed, Your honor.
昨天，他的父亲，一位优秀的整形外科医生
Yesterday, his father, a prominent plastic surgeon,
在家中使用厨房刀具
Allegedly killed his mother with a kitchen knife
杀害了这个孩子的母亲
in their shadyside home.
啊
What?
什么？什……
What? Wh...
什么
What?
我……不，不行……
I'm... no. No...
我不……我不会处理这个案子的
I'm not...I'm not supposed to be dealing with this.
Mr. Fallin，请坐下，Mr. Fallin
Mr. Fallin, take a seat, Please. Mr. Fallin.
Mr. Fallin, Take a seat, please. Mr. Fallin!
这是怎么了
What's going on?
我……我也不知道
I... I don't know.
Mr. Fallin!
Mr. Fallin，站住
Mr. Fallin! Stop!
Wendling法官裁定择日再审
Judge Wendling issued a continuance!
他命令你周五要回到法庭上来
He's ordered you to return to court on Friday!
如果你届时不出席法庭的话，就判你藐视法庭
He'll find you in contempt if you fail to appear!
嘿，你听见我说的了吗
Hey! Are you Listening to me?
那到底是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me
我不知道
I didn't know.
你不知道
You didn't know?
Mr. Fallin，我们一天要处理50个案子
Mr. Fallin, we get 50 cases a day.
为啥把那孩子领到那儿去
Why was that kid even there?
他的爸爸在24小时前才刚刚杀害了他的妈妈
His father murdered his mother 24 hours ago
然后你们的人就今天就拉着他上了法庭
And you people haul him in for a formality?
你周五早上必须出庭
You are gonna be in court on Friday morning.
我建议你尽快抽空
I suggest you make an appointment
去见见Hunter
to see Hunter As soon as possible.
他的姥姥，姥爷去哪了
Where are his grandparents?!
他们在伦敦开往纽约的游船上呢
They're on a cruise from London to New York.
他们周三早上就会回来的
They'll be back on Thursday morning.
Gretchen...
快去会议室，已经开了43分钟了
Conference room. 43 minutes ago.
好的
Ok.
他来了
He's here.
Nick……能等等再说吗
Nick... Can it wait?
Nick，你的缓刑监督官正在等你，你……
Nick! Your probation officers are waiting, And you...
早上好，Mr.Fallin
Good morning, Mr. Fallin.
这是强制执行的
It's mandatory
你紧张了吗
Stressed?
噢，你不会知道的
Oh, you have no idea.
那么现在我来解释一下这个问题……
So I'm gonna drive this point home...
我请大家翻开你们面前的提议案，看看第二页
I'd like you to turn your attention to page 2 of our proposal,
第4段，开头写着“税法”的那个地方
Paragraph 4 that Starts with "Tax laws."
形势已经有所变化，我认为这样的话
The conditions have changed, I think in such a way
你们来我们这座城市是非常有好处的
to make it extremely conducive to you coming to our city.
Nick!
我正向Mr.Swann和他的同事们解释
I just was explaining to Mr. Swann and his associates
新税法和建筑建设规章制度
that we feel the new tax laws and building regulations
这将对Swann科技公司非常有益
Could be manipulated to benefit
只要我们能够尽快达成
As long as we can get this
和Netbugh公司的协议
deal with Netburgh closed as soon as possible.
早上好
Good morning.
昨天我已经向Netburgh公司提出正式要约
I gave the formal offer to the gentlemen at Netburgh yesterday.
他们的人正在认真考虑这件事
They're taking it into serious consideration.
今天结束前，我们就应该得到他们的答复……
We should have a response by day's end...
Netburgh公司还没有答复吗
Netburgh hasn't responded?
还没有
Not yet.
他们都是一群19岁的孩子
They're a bunch of 19-year-old kids
是从一件旧仓库发展起来的
Working out of an old warehouse.
请撤回要约
Take it off the table.
呃，抱歉
Uh, excuse me?
200万美金已经是个非常慷慨的数目了
$2 million was more than a generous offer.
我可没兴趣继续等
I'm not interested in waiting any longer
他们的答复了
for their response.
今天就撤回要约
Take it off the table today,
明天请重新拟一份100万美金的要约
Make an offer of a million tomorrow.
如果那就是你想要做的，那么当然可以
If that's the way you'd like to play this, then sure.
是的，好的
Yes. Fine.
现在，我们得到
Now, do we have permission
县委委员的许可了吗
from the County Commissioner?
也不是了
Not exactly.
县政府正在考虑
The city is considering
承担基础设施建设的费用，前提是我们可以……
covering infrastructure costs if we can...
哦噢，哦噢，Mr. Fallin，我们每等一天
Whoa, whoa, Mr. Fallin. Every day we wait,
我们就要出更多的钱
We hemorrhage more money.
是的，我明白，县委委员
Yes, I understand that. The county commissioner
需要签署我的财政预算草案……
needs to sign off on my budget proposal...
不，不，不，不行，我们……我们不能……我们不能这么结束
No, no, no, no. We... we cannot... We cannot close this deal.
这些事情需要运作一阵子，Mr. Swann
These things take a little massaging, Mr. Swann.
如果你愿意坐下稍等一下的话
If you'd just like to take a seat for a second,
我可以马上为你接通县委委员的电话
I can get The county Commissioner on the phone right now.
我不知道在Pittsburgh那里是怎样的
I don't know how things work in Pittsburgh,
不过在我们那里
But where we come from,
金钱就是一切
money matters.
我们公司每年可以带来5亿美元的收入
My company brings in $500 million annually.
任何一个城市在我们面前都得卑躬屈膝
Any city would bend over to have us,
更不必说那些中等乡镇，他们的大型工业
Let alone some mid-sized town whose major industry
早在20年前就完蛋了
Up and died Some 20 years ago.
同志们我们走
Gentlemen.
现在，没有比这更好的结局了
Now, that couldn't have gone better.
Nicholas.
来我办公室
My office.
爹
Dad?
坐
Sit down.
儿子……
Son...
你还想当这家事务所的的合伙人吗……
Do you want to make partner with this firm...
想还是不想
or not?
那么，刚才在那边是怎么了
Now, what the hell was that out there?
你为啥迟到了45分钟
Why were you 45 minutes late?
你为什么不和那些县委员们
Why didn't you get that contract
达成协议呢
to the county Commissioner?
不要再像刚才那样
And don't ever embarrass me
在我们的客户面前让我丢脸
Like that again In front of a client.
那家伙就是个混蛋
That guy's an ass.
那他也是我们客户
He's also a client
他有权利要求我们
He has a right to expect us
做好充分准备
to go in there prepared.
好吧，撤回Netburgh公司的要约
All right. Pull the Netburgh offer
然后重新和县委委员谈谈
And get over to the County Commissioner
这样你才能把你弄的烂摊子
So you can back up that crap
收拾好
You were spewing out in there.
好的
Yes, sir.
Nicholas.
假如我有你那样的才能……
If I had your talent...
如果我有你一半的才华
If I had half your talent,
我10年前……
I would have retired...
恐怕就退休了
10 years ago.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
那可不是夸你
That's not a compliment.
尽职调查进行到哪了
Where are we on due diligence?
我们就要完成了，助理律师……
We're just about done. The paralegal...
公司文件呢
Incorporation papers?
正在进行公证，不过……
Working on the notary, but...
安排我和Netburgh的那帮孩子在进行一次会面
Get me another meeting with the Netburgh kids.
另外，调查一下一个叫Thomas Reed的大夫的庭审记录
Also, run a court record check on a Dr. Thomas Reed.
看看都有什么情况
That's 2 ES. See what that name brings up.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
我也不知道，就是你查好了告诉我
I don't know. You tell me.
你不接我电话
You don't return my calls.
你不能这么办事
You don't make this deal,
马上就要选举了，你这样做可是很蠢的
You're gonna look pretty stupid come election time.
听着，这个交易会让这座城市
Look, this deal is gonna cost the city
入不敷出，这你也知道
more than it brings in, and you know that.
他们既不想交税
They don't want to pay city tax,
也不想承担基础设施建设的费用
And they don't want to cover their infrastructure costs.
你已经担起了
You have done jack
推动这座城市经济的重任
to boost this city's economy
不要以为我不会告诉大家
and don't think I won't let it be known.
你就是导致交易破裂的家伙
that your office was the deal-breaker.
好吧
All right.
我们来负担基础设施建设
We'll eat infrastructure
还免除他们7年的税收
And 7 years of taxes.
之后，愿上帝帮助我……
After that, So help me god...
那之后的事情，留到7年后再说吧
We'll speak in 7 years.
Allegheny儿童福利院
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
我来找Hunter Reed，我之前预约过了
Hunter Reed? I have an appointment.
嘿，Hunter
Hey, hunter.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
几天后我们还要出席一次听证会
We have a second shelter hearing coming up in a few days.
你自己决定，你要么和你的姥姥，姥爷住在一起
It's your call. Either you live with your grandparents
要么让福利院给你安排一个寄养家庭
or social services is gonna put you in a foster home.
你打算怎么处理
What was your deal?
一言难尽啊
That's a long story.
你不想接手这个案子，对吧
You don't want to be doing this, do you?
说实话，不，我不想
Truth be told, No, I don't.
那你为什么还要做
Then why are you?
你想要换个律师吗
You want another lawyer?
我那样说过吗
Did I say that?
我因为犯了法被判罚进行社会公益劳动
I got sentenced to community service for breaking the law.
你干了些什么
What'd you do?
你想为我那天的行为道歉吗
You want me to apologize for the way I acted?
是做了坏事吗
Something bad?
没有
No.
只是干了些蠢事
Just something stupid.
啥事啊
What?
我因为吸毒被捕，可以了吧
I got arrested for drugs, ok?
不介意我坐下吧
You mind if I sit down?
我像你这么大的时候，我妈妈去世了
My mom died when I was about your age.
怎么去世的
How?
癌症
Cancer.
你亲眼看到她死去吗
Did you see her die?
我认为我爸爸爱我的妈妈
I thought my dad loved my mom.
为什么他要伤害她
Why would he hurt her?
他拿刀捅了她好几下
He stabbed her so many times.
为什么
Why?
Allegheny县监狱
是Reed医生吗
Dr. Reed?
我是Nicholas Fallin，我是你儿子的辩护律师
My name is Nicholas Fallin. I'm your son's attorney.
很快会召开听证会
There's going to be a shelter hearing
是关于Hunter的监护权的
in regards to Hunter's custody.
我需要你签署这个宣誓书
I need you to sign an affidavit
证明你已经得知听证会的消息了
Stating that you've been given notice of the hearing.
我儿子在哪儿
Where is my son?
你儿子在一家临时收容所
Your son is in a temporary shelter.
为什么
Why?
你不知道
You don't know?
我……
I...
你不知道你为什么在这里吗
Do you know why you're in here?
因为我应该签这个文件
Because I'm supposed to sign this form.
是的
Yes.
你知道，Nick，我已经动用了我所有的关系
You know, Nick, I had to use all my contacts
才查到这些的
in the precinct to get this.
Thomas Reed医生在他24岁的时候，企图自杀过
Dr. Thomas Reed tried to off himself when he was 24.
在他当时实习的医院里面
Got a bunch of morphine from the hospital
弄到了一些吗啡
Where he was interning.
幸好被一个朋友及时发现了
A friend found him before it was too late.
接受过精神辅导吗
Psychiatric help?
在Western医院做过6个月的门诊病人
6 months outpatient treatment at Western.
那之后就没有任何记录了
Nothing on the books since then.
他的主治医生叫做Milton Samuels
Doctor's name was Milton Samuels.
很好
Great.
那么，是哪阵香风把您吹来了
So, what made you decide to call me?
10年前，你治疗过一个叫做Thomas Reed的病人
10 years ago you treated a patient named Thomas Reed.
我恐怕不能帮你忙，Mr.Fallin
I'm afraid I can't Help you, mr. Fallin.
我找到了Alvin Masterson，另外这有你爸爸的电话
I've got Alvin Masterson and your father holding.
喂
Yeah.
3年前，一个叫做Sue Pence的人
3 years ago, one Sue Pence filed
曾经对Thomas Reed医生提起过医疗过失赔偿
a malpractice claim against a Dr.Thomas Reed.
Reed医生很明显搞砸了她的整形手术
Dr. Reed apparently screwed up her facelift.
好，再见，后来呢
Ok, bye. What happened?
庭外私了了，只是按键通话了几次
Settled out of court. Just press talk.
3个月后，一个叫做Amy Taupin的人又对他提起了类似的诉讼
3 months later, Amy Taupin filed a similar suit,
还是私了了，8个月后，还有一起类似的诉讼
Also settled out of court. 8 months later, Another settlement.
嘿伙计们，他来了
Hey guys! He's here.
Netburgh公司
嘿
Hey.
Sal Sessio, Amanda Holtz.
嗨，很高兴见到你
Hi. Nice to meet you.
这是新的要约
Here's the counter.
新要约，原来的那份呢
Counter? What about the first offer?
听着，这就是生意场的规则
Listen, this is how business is done.
你收到要约，你要做出答复
You receive an offer, you respond to that offer.
拖得时间太久了，要约就要撤回来
You wait too long, it gets pulled off the table.
这个价格更低
This is less.
的确
True.
只有一半
Half.
孩子们，你们有24小时时间考虑接受还是不接受
You have 24 hours, kids. Take it or leave it.
得了吧，首先，我不是你的孩子
Ok, first of all, I'm not your kid.
明白吗，第二，我可以和Intel公司做这笔交易
Ok? Secondly, I can make this deal with Intel
我只要拿起话筒打个电话即可
Just by picking up the phone.
那你就快打个电话吧
Then pick it up.
我和Hunter见面了
I met with Hunter.
他要我帮他拿些衣服
He asked me to pick up some more clothes for him.
然后呢
So?
然后我发现我进不去他的家
So I can't go to his house
除非有社会公益服务人员陪同
Without someone from social services.
Laurie Solt，社会公益服务部门
Laurie Solt, Social services.
我们来这儿给那孩子拿些衣服
We're here to pick up some clothes for the boy.
好的，女士，请便
Yes, ma'am. It's Ok.
太像Norman Rockwell的风格了（著名画家）
It's so Norman Rockwell.
还有一把Norman Rockwell风格的菜刀
With a knife.
Dr. Samuels.
你去干嘛了
What are you doing?
我去趟洗手间
Just took a leak.
怎么了
What?
搜
Go.
氟非那嗪（一种安定药）
副作用
抖动
果然
Bingo.
怎么了
What's up?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
试着查找一种新药的信息
Trying to find some information on a new drug.
哦，我来吧
Oh, here.
就是它
That's it.
就是它，就是它
That's it. That's it.
晚安
Good night.
Reed医生是因为抖动的厉害
Did Dr. Reed stop taking the Fluphenazine
才停止服用氟非那嗪的吗
Because of his tremor?
是的
Yes.
然后你就给他开了一种未经批准的药来代替吗
And you prescribed a non-approved drug in its place.
我给他登记过临床药物试验
I enrolled him in the clinical trial.
Reed医生知道可能存在风险
Dr. Reed knew of the risks.
他不顾一切想要找到一种药
He was desperate to find the drug
找一种没有那么严重副作用的药
that didn't have such an acute side effect.
好吧，药物试验什么时候开始的
Well, when did the trial begin?
3周前
3 weeks ago.
氟非那嗪在人体内需要多长时间
And how long does it take the Fluphenazine
消除药效
to clear the system?
4-6周时间
4 to 6 weeks.
那么就是说有可能这些药物作用已经相互冲突了
So it's possible the drugs may have counteracted each other.
我知道精神分裂症的事情了
I know about the schizophrenia.
也知道药物试验的事情
And the drug trials.
我还知道关于医疗过失诉讼的事
I know about the malpractice suits
以及你正在服用的安定药的副作用
And the side effects of the antipsychotic you were taking.
你有没有想到，Reed医生
Did it ever occur to you, Dr. Reed,
氟非那嗪和你的新药
That the fluphenazine And the new drug
可能和另一种药相互冲突了
May have counteracted one another...
从而导致你袭击了你的妻子
And caused you to attack your wife?
如果你不和你的律师
If you don't talk to your attorney
说有关你精神分裂症病史的话
about your Psychiatric history,
你可能会面临终生监禁的判决
You're gonna face a life sentence.
你现在可以保持沉默
Now, you can keep your mouth shut
你也可以失去一切
And you can lose everything,
或者你可以以你精神失常免除谋杀指控
or, you can plea-bargain your way out of the murder charges
然后接受辩诉交易
on a clear-cut insanity defense
同时还可以向药物公司提起民事诉讼
While concurrently filing a civil suit against the drug company
这样会对你的儿子有很大好处
That will benefit your son greatly.
他现在怎么样
How is he?
法院想要把他从你身边带走
The state wants to take him away from you
你这一辈子都将见不到他
for the rest of your life.
我该怎么做
What should I do?
威胁说你要自杀，Reed医生
Threaten to kill yourself, Dr. Reed.
那样可以为我们争取一些时间
That'll buy us some time.
州法律规定有自杀倾向的犯人
State law requires that a suicidal inmate
要被遣送到精神病院
be transferred to a psychiatric ward.
你就威胁要自杀，把你的精神病史
Do that. Let's reveal your history
还有你参加药物试验的事情都抖出来
And your participation in the drug trials.
转告我的儿子……
Tell my son...
告诉他我非常爱他
Tell Hunter I Love him very much.
Masterson在……
Masterson's on...
请稍等
Just a minute.
Alvin，Mr. Fallin想要见你
Alvin, Mr. Fallin's here to see you.
我接到社会公益服务部门的电话
I received a call from social services.
说你们去Reed家里转悠去了
Said you went to the Reed house to snoop around.
是的，我需要了解更多的信息
Yeah. I needed some more information
关于发生了什么……
about the events that took place...
你还可能需要什么信息
What information could you possibly need?
那男孩的父亲会因为
This boy's father is gonna be criminally prosecuted
谋杀罪被起诉，他妈妈已经死了
For murder. His mother's dead.
他的姥姥，姥爷是最合适的监护人
The grandparents are perfectly suitable guardians.
我发现了一些事情
I discovered some things
可能会改变事情的结果……
That could change the outcome of...
我可没告诉你去调查这个谋杀案
I did not tell you to investigate a murder.
我就告诉你去为这孩子辩护了
I told you to advocate for a child.
你等等
Hang on a second.
我决定我……好了，不要说了
I thought that I was... Well, don't!
只要按照我的规则行事就好了，知道吗
Just follow my rules, ok?
如果你的规则是错的会怎么样
What if your rules are wrong?
你听着，我不是在求你
Look, I didn't ask for you.
我这是在帮你，因为我是看着你父亲的面子
I'm doing you a favor because I respect your father,
他是个比你强10倍的好律师
A man who is clearly 10 times the lawyer you are.
现在，如果你更想去Stanton法官那里
Now, if you prefer to return to judge Stanton
去找你的另外选择
And explore your other option,
我相信那将会是蹲监狱
Which I understood to be jail time,
那么你可以走
Then you may.
只是记住一点
But know one thing.
只要我还在充当你的看管人
As long as I act as your warden
只要你还在我手下工作
And you are serving your time in my facility,
你就得按着我的规矩来
You will do things my way,
否者我会把你送回法官那里
or I will send you back faster than it used to take you
比送黑8入洞还要快，你的明白（9球中，黑8入洞就要结束了）
to snort an 8-ball. Got it?
你有没有觉得有时候你会听见一些东西
You ever think you hear something
而事实上你并没有听见
That you didn't really hear?
像是晚上的动静什么的
Like a noise at night?
像是有一种声音，或者感觉像是有人在叫你名字
Like a noise or someone calling your name?
有的，我想
Yeah, I guess.
有的人会得一种病
Some people have a sickness,
一种叫做精神分裂症的疾病
A disease called schizophrenia,
那种病就能让人听见像那样的声音
That can make them hear voices like that.
这种声音会让人非常害怕别人
And the voices can make them very afraid of people.
极度的恐惧，他们就会做出可怕的事情
So afraid, They do terrible things.
我爸就是这样吗
Is that what's wrong with my dad?
是的
Yes.
好吧，如果他有了病
Well, if he was sick,
为什么他不去看病呢
Why didn't he See a doctor?
他去了，但是医生
He did, but the doctor gave him
给他服用了错药
the wrong medication.
那就是原因吗
Is that why?
我觉得是
I think so.
好吧，那他现在服用的是正确的药吗
Well, does he have the right medicine now?
是的
Yes.
所以他会好起来，然后我就可以回家了吗
So he'll be better, And I can go back home?
可能不会那么简单
It may not be that easy.
如果他能好起来的话，我想和他在一起
If he can get better, I want to be with him.
很明显，这件案子会涉及数百万的赔偿
There's clearly a multi-million dollar verdict in this case.
你会把这好事让给我吗
And you're giving this to me?
不，不，我们分享
No, no. We're sharing it.
我不能马上接手这个案子
I can't handle the case right now.
我是个证人，我现在代表着那孩子
I'm a witness. I'm representing a child
如果和解不成的话
Who may become an adverse party
他可能会成为一个他方当事人
If reconciliation Doesn't take place.
所以你让我来倒霉是吗
So you want me to bust my balls
同时你却坐等着收大头的钱
While you get the lion's share of the money.
不，这是个很矛盾的事
No, it's a conflict.
Reed医生是他妻子的财产受益人
Dr. Reed is the beneficiary of his wife's estate,
但是他同时又因为她的死而被指控
But he's being criminally prosecuted for her death.
那么他妻子的财产就应该由Hunter继承
The wife's estate then switches to Hunter,
而Hunter是未成年人，他没有法律上的行为能力
Who can't do anything of his own free will because he's a minor.
所以不管谁成为他的监护人
So whoever is the guardian,
不管是他的父亲还是他的姥姥，姥爷
Either the father or the grandparents,
他们都将对这起诉讼负责
They will be responsible for filing the suit.
那么，他爸爸起诉医生医治不当
So, the father sues the doctor for malpractice,
起诉制药公司负责产品责任
The pharmaceutical company for product liability,
并且利用他的儿子遭受的痛苦来博得同情
And collects for the son's suffering
而这一切都是因为他杀死了他的妻子
All because he killed his own wife?
正是如此
Exactly.
于是你就将这个公益案子转成了有利可赚的案子了
Leave it to you to turn pro bono into profit.
我刚和Swann通过话
I just spoke to Swann.
如果截止到明天早上他还没有看到完整的文件的话
If he doesn't see the completed paperwork
他就会退出交易
by tomorrow morning, He is pulling out.
完全退出
Altogether.
喝茶吗
Tea?
妈，妈，妈妈哎
Uh, mom, mom. Mom!
……@#￥%……
你对我们承诺的是两倍的钱和股票期权
Ok, you promised us twice the money and stock options.
好的，听我说
Ok, listen to me.
你收到要约，然后你作出答复
You get an offer, you respond to that offer.
你拖得太久的话，要约就会撤销
You wait too long, It gets pulled off the table.
好吧，我理解，但是我向大家承诺的比这要多
Ok, I understand that, But I promised everyone more.
那就是我们的要约
That's our offer.
我……我不想这样，那我不能接受
I... I don't want it, then. I can't.
好
Ok.
好的
那我告辞了
Excuse me.
先生
Mister.
妈，妈，求你了，先生
Mom. Mom! Please, mister.
他只是太年轻，他还不知道钱又多难挣
He's just young. He doesn't know what money is.
他太年轻了，我们需要钱
He's just young. We need the money.
我都交不起他的学费了
I can't pay for his school anymore.
以前他还有个叔叔可以帮他，但是他……
We used to have an uncle. He was helping, but he...
你想怎样
What's it gonna be
1.8.
1.5.
20000股
20,000 shares.
1.5，15000股
1.5, 15,000 shares.
还要给我妈妈的家人
And an apartment in Budapest
在Budapest买一栋公寓
For my mother's family.
成交
Ok.
太好了
Yes!
Yes.
哦，谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
谢谢你，谢谢
Thank you! Thank you!
需要帮忙吗
Need some help?
你想拍马屁可是拍错人了
You're kissing the wrong ass.
感觉怎样
So, what's it like?
什么啊
What?
儿童法律服务部
Children's Legal Services.
我不知道
I don't know.
你在那里有一段时间了啊
You're spending a lot of time there.
要学的东西还很多
It's a steep learning curve.
你有没有觉得你现在做的事情很有意义
Do you feel like you're doing something meaningful?
我觉得我就是在执行对我的判决而已
I feel like I'm serving my sentence.
这个才有意义呢
This is meaningful.
这是关于钱的事
This is about money.
我说的就是那个
That's what I'm saying.
我不知道
I don't know.
如果我没有欠那么大一笔学校贷款
If I hadn't run up such huge school loans,
我很愿意去公益部门工作的
I'd be working in public service.
你笑什么啊
What?
我觉得你是个骗子，你只是没有意识到这一点而已
I think you're a shark. You just don't know it yet.
我爸爸总是告诉我说不要为赚钱而苦恼
My father always told me not to worry about making money,
而是要担心不能有所作为
But to worry about making a difference.
好吧，挣钱就能有所作为啊
Well, money makes a difference.
相信我
Believe me.
那些拿最低工资的整天大呼小叫的人
All the man-hours scraping around for minimum wage,
他们创造的价值和你能够创造的价值
They can't compete with the huge influx of money
不可同日而语
That you are capable of generating.
先赚足了钱
Make the money first,
那时候，如果你还想有所作为的话
Then if you still feel like it,
那你就去做公益吧
Then go make a difference.
我觉得你这是在演戏
I think you're putting on an act.
我要去复印这些文件了
I have to get these copies made.
喂
Hello?
Nick，我是James
Nick, it's James.
Thomas Reed昨天晚上威胁说要自杀
Thomas Reed threatened to kill himself last night.
他们刚刚将他送到了精神病院
They just moved him to western.
谢谢你，谢谢了
Thank you. Thanks.
我已经见过本案中的姥姥姥爷
I've met the grandparents in question.
社会福利部门认为他们
Social services considers them
是这个孩子的合适的监护人
to be an appropriate placement for the child.
如果没有异议的话
Unless there are any objections,
我将会赋予
I will grant permanent custody
Phyllis和Donald Sample夫妇永久监护权
to Phyllis and Donald Sample,
也就是Hunter的外祖父母
Hunter's maternal grandparents.
Bailiff，下一个待审案子是哪个
Bailiff, what's the next case on the docket?
法官大人
Your honor.
什么事，Mr.Fallin
Yes, Mr. Fallin?
我的当事人希望和他的父亲在一起
My client would like to go back to his father.
法官大人，Hunter的监护权归属问题不能拖到明年
Your honor, Hunter can't just sit in limbo for the next year
等他父亲的刑事诉讼判决后在处理就太晚了
Awaiting the outcome of a clear-cut criminal case.
你应该知道的，Mr.Fallin，你的当事人的父亲
You are aware, Mr. Fallin, That your client's father
已经被指控有谋杀罪
has been charged with murder?
我明白此时此刻
I understand that at the moment
Reed医生无法行使监护权
Dr. Reed is in no position to take custody.
然而，如果因为某种原因
However, If by some chance
Reed医生没有被判谋杀罪
Dr. Reed is cleared of criminal charges
而且已经恢复了权利的话
And rehabilitated,
Hunter是不是有可能回家呢
Wouldn't it be possible that Hunter might return home?
是的，有可能
Yes, it's possible.
法官大人，这非常不符合常理
Your honor, This is highly unusual.
我明白，我只是在要求
I understand. I only ask
在Hunter的父亲判决之前，只是判给他的外祖父母
That the grandparents' custody be represented as temporary,
暂时的监护权
Pending The criminal trial.
法官大人，他的外祖父母……
Your honor, The grandpar...
我仅仅只是陈述我的当事人的愿望
I am simply representing my client's desire
希望有机会可以和父亲团聚
to be given the chance to be reunited with his father
法庭应该认为这是很合适的
Should the court deem it appropriate.
他只是希望有这个机会，法官大人
He just wants the chance, your honor.
好的，Mr. Fallin
Ok, Mr. Fallin.
在Reed医生的刑事判决出来之前
I will grant temporary custody
我只赋予他的外祖父母暂时的监护权
pending the outcome of Dr. Reed's criminal trial.
Gretchen……去会议室，开了18分钟了
Gretchen... Conference room, 18 minutes ago.
你没有权利作出这种交易
You had no authority to make this kind of deal.
谈判时，他们很强硬
They drove a hard bargain.
你没有权利
You had no authority.
我们这里，钱决定一切
Where I come from, money matters.
你什么意思
What was that?
你正错过一笔利润丰厚的交易
You're passing up an incredible deal
这一切就是为了你的妄自尊大
All for the sake of your enormous ego.
我自大
My ego?
我们的小城镇愿意
Our little town is willing
承担基础设施建设的费用
to eat your infrastructure costs
而且免除你们
And give you 7 years
七年的税收
Living off The fat of our land.
总之，我刚刚给你安排的交易
All in all, I just did a deal
会在未来五年内给你带来将近2亿美元的收益
Worth nearly $20 million to you over the next half decade,
而你却为了眼前这个收益的1/10的
And you're sweating over cash and stock options
现金和股票纠缠不休
Worth a tenth of that.
那么县委会为我们在行驶车道旁
And will the city build us an off-ramp
修一条驶出匝道吗，会的
from the parkway? Yes.
会给我吗停车设施的建设许可吗
Building permits for the parking structure?
会的
Yes.
我们会在一年之后入驻
We'll move in after the first of the year.
你们能到我们这里入驻真是我们的荣幸
It's an honor to have your business.
非常期待你们的到来
Anxious to get to work.
干得不错
Terrific.
干得好
Good going.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
不必客气
Pleasure.
呃，那个在Budapest的公寓……
Uh, that apartment in Budapest...
是的
Yeah.
Nicholas.
来我办公室
My office.
我知道刚才我的谈判有点不符合常理
I know that was a little unconventional.
看着我，Nicholas
Look me in the eye, Nicholas.
我们达成了交易
We got the account.
这不是道歉的时候
This is not the time to apologize.
西南精神病院
我一会儿来找你
I'll get you in a minute.
办法奏效了
It worked.
法庭同意暂时把Hunter的监护权给他的外祖父母
The state has agreed to call the custody temporary.
你还有机会和你儿子在一起
There's still a chance to be with your son.
Dr. Reed?
我的儿子是我在这个世界上最爱的人，Mr. Fallin
I love my son more than anything in this world, Mr. Fallin.
我会……我会提出自己精神不正常的辩护
I'll... I'll plead insanity.
我会起诉制药公司
I'll sue the pharmaceutical company
来为Hunter做出赔偿
to provide for Hunter.
但是我现在不能再当他的爸爸了
But I can't be his father anymore.
他是你儿子
He's your son.
我杀了他妈妈
I killed his mother.
我知道我做了什么
I know what I did.
我现在知道了
I know now.
我做了那种没人性的事情……
I did that...
而且他看到了这一切
And he saw.
但是他想要原谅你
He wants to forgive you.
但是……
But...
你是我，你会怎么做
What would you do?
我不会就这么走开
Well, I wouldn't just walk away.
如果我有像那样的儿子的话
If I had a son like that,
我不会放弃了解他的机会的
I wouldn't give up the chance to know him,
也不会放弃让他了解我的机会
to have him know me.
看……
See...
我不能
I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不会就这么不管的，Reed医生
I'm not going away, Dr. Reed.
替我照顾好Hunter
Take care of Hunter for me.
他还没有准备好
He's not ready yet.
为什么
Why not?
他需要一些时间
He needs some time.
你还好吧
You all right?
不好
No.
对不起
I'm sorry.
法外情真贴吧倾力制作
谢谢观看
他只是需要一些时间，Hunter
He just needs some time, Hunter.